<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Serene</string>

    <string name="serene_introduction_1">Before that, i need you to know each category of Self-care. \n\nIt won’t take a lot of your time, we just want to let you know what is this app all about</string>
    <string name="serene_introduction_2">Based on Catherine Beard, M.A. of Health of Wellness Coaching, Integrative Health Practice, \n\nThere are 7 Category of Self-care Activities</string>

    <string name="serene_selfcare_activity_emotional">Embrace your feelings, understand their whispers and treat yourself with gentle understanding.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_activity_environmental">Breathe life into your surroundings and respect the delicate harmony of the world.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_activity_mental">Tidy up your thoughts, cultivate calm, and savor the silence of a peaceful mind.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_activity_physical">Keep your psych up and fuel your body’s fire to feel the strength bloom within.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_activity_recreational">Unleash your inner child, let your soul revel in the joy of play.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_activity_social">Stitch love into shared laughter and bask in the warmth of belonging.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_activity_spiritual">Dive deep within, uncover your purpose\'s flame, and let your spirit dance to its own rhythm.</string>

    <string name="serene_selfcare_result_emotional">Learn healthy coping mechanisms for stress and negativity, and remember to celebrate your victories with open arms. This is where you dance with joy, embrace tears, and discover the strength within your emotional tapestry.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_result_environmental">Honor your deep connection to the Earth in this verdant space. Step outside, feel the sun on your skin, and breathe in the fresh air. Practice sustainable habits, minimize your environmental impact, and appreciate the beauty that surrounds you.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_result_mental">Step into the tranquil haven of your mind. Embrace mindfulness practices like meditation, journaling, or simply breathing deeply. Let go of anxieties like fallen leaves, and nourish your inner garden with affirmations and self-compassion.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_result_physical">Listen to the whispers of your body, this sacred temple that houses your spirit. Fuel your energy with nourishing foods and prioritize quality sleep to nurture this precious vessel. Remember, a healthy body is the foundation for a vibrant life.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_result_recreational">Let your inner child loose. Explore new hobbies, rediscover old passions, and allow yourself the freedom to express without judgment. These are the threads that weave the tapestry of your unique spirit.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_result_social">Make time for the people who make you feel seen and heard, engage in meaningful conversations, and build a support network that fosters belonging and joy. We are social creatures, and connection is vital for our well-being.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_result_spiritual">Find solace in meditation, prayer, or simply spending time in nature. Seek meaning and purpose beyond the daily grind, and explore practices that connect you to your inner self and the universe around you.</string>

    <string name="serene_selfcare_introduction_emotional">involves taking care of matters of the heart with healthy coping strategies and self-compassion.\n\nIt helps you understand yourself more, better deal with challenges and setbacks, and develop healthy emotional responses.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_introduction_environmental">involves taking care of the spaces and places around you.\n\nThe more you take care of your immediate environment, the more it will help you to thrive and feel a sense of belonging where you are.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_introduction_mental">is about cultivating a healthy mindset through mindfulness and curiosity.\n\nIt is important for developing a healthy mindset, growing your skills, reducing stress, and enhancing your knowledge and creativity.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_introduction_physical">involves taking care of your body.\n\nWhen you practice activities for your physical well-being, you can increase your energy levels and boost your self-esteem.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_introduction_recreational">involves taking care of your inner child with hobbies, fun activities, and new experiences.\n\nRecreation is important because it lets you get away from the pressure of your to-do list and simply enjoy the pleasures that life has to offer. </string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_introduction_social">means cultivating healthy relationships and connecting with people who get you.\n\n Seeking out positive social connections helps us create a sense of belonging and acceptance.</string>
    <string name="serene_selfcare_introduction_spiritual">involves taking care of your soul through activities or practices that provide a sense of purpose, direction, or meaning to your life.\n\nIt can help you find more meaning in life, feel more grounded, and develop a sense of belonging in life.</string>


</resources>